Guide to the William T. Grant Foundation records FA004
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant files, 1940-1990s, bulk 1970-1985; 1970-1985; 3; Tavistock Institute of Human Relations; Spock, Benjamin (1903-1998); Freud, Anna (1895-1982); Hampstead Child-Therapy Clinic; Goodall, Jane (1934); 96.9 Cubic Feet 246 letter document boxes, 5 legal document boxes, 4 half-legal boxes, 1 card f
  - Grant files, 1970s - 1990s, bulk 1980s; 1980-1989; B
    - Emory University - Finance - Margaret Beale Spencer, Ph.D. (86-1086-86), 1986-1989 (Box 177, Folder 2189)
    - Emory University - Final Report - Margaret Beale Spencer, Ph.D. (86-1086-86), 1988 (Box 177, Folder 2190)
    - Emory University - Report - Margaret Beale Spencer, Ph.D. (86-1086-86), 1988 (Box 177, Folder 2191)
    - Emory University - Margaret Beale Spencer, Ph.D. (86-1086-86), 1986 (Box 177, Folder 2192)
    - Erikson Institute - Administration - James Garbarino (86-1090-86), 1986-1987 (Box 177, Folder 2193)
    - Erikson Institute - Application - James Garbarino (86-1090-86), 1986-1987 (Box 177, Folder 2194)
    - Erikson Institute - General Correspondence - James Garbarino (86-1090-86), 1988-1989 (Box 177, Folder 2195)
    - Erikson Institute - Final Report - James Garbarino (86-1090-86), 1987 (Box 177, Folder 2196)
    - Erikson Institute - Finance - James Garbarino (86-1090-86), 1986-1987 (Box 177, Folder 2197)
    - Erikson Institute - James Garbarino (86-1090-86), 1986-1987 (Box 177, Folder 2198)
    - Erikson Institute - Administration - Frances M. Stott (83-0893-00), 1982-1986 (Box 177, Folder 2199)
    - Erikson Institute - Application - Frances M. Stott (83-0893-00), 1982-1983 (Box 177, Folder 2200)
    - Erikson Institute - Final Report - Frances M. Stott (83-0893-00), 1986 (Box 177, Folder 2201)
    - Erikson Institute - Finance - Frances M. Stott (83-0893-00), 1983-1986 (Box 177, Folder 2202)
    - Erikson Institute - Reports - Frances M. Stott (83-0893-00), 1984-1985 (Box 177, Folder 2203)
    - Erikson Institute - Frances M. Stott (83-0893-00), 1983 (Box 177, Folder 2204)
    - Family Dynamics - Administration - Derek V. Schuster, Ed.D. (82-0805-00), 1981-1982 (Box 178, Folder 2205)
    - Family Dynamics - Application - Derek V. Schuster, Ed.D. (82-0805-00), 1981-1985 (Box 178, Folder 2206)
    - Family Dynamics - Finance - Derek V. Schuster, Ed.D. (82-0805-00), 1983 (Box 178, Folder 2207)
    - Family Service Association of America - Administration - Dorothy Fahs Beck (82-0823-00), 1982-1984 (Box 178, Folder 2208)
    - Family Service Association of America - Applications - Dorothy Fahs Beck (82-0823-00), 1982-1983 (Box 178, Folder 2209)
    - Family Service Association of America - Finance - Dorothy Fahs Beck (82-0823-00), 1984 (Box 178, Folder 2210)
    - Family Service Association of America - Reports - Dorothy Fahs Beck (82-0823-00), 1983-1984 (Box 178, Folder 2211)
    - Family Service Association of America - Dorothy Fahs Beck (82-0823-00), 1982 (Box 178, Folder 2212)
    - Family Service Association of America - Administration - Mrs. C. Reynolds Pratt (82-0849-00), 1982-1985 (Box 178, Folder 2213)
    - Family Service Association of America - Applikcation - Mrs. C. Reynolds Pratt (82-0849-00), 1982-1984 (Box 178, Folder 2214)
    - Family Service Association of America - Final Report - Mrs. C. Reynolds Pratt (82-0849-00), 1983-1985 (Box 178, Folder 2215)
    - Family Service Association of America - Finance - Mrs. C. Reynolds Pratt (82-0849-00), 1983-1985 (Box 178, Folder 2216)
    - Family Service Association of Nassau County - Administration - Salvatore Ambrosino, Ed.D. (86-1100-86), 1986-1988 (Box 178, Folder 2217)
    - Family Service Association of Nassau County - Application - Salvatore Ambrosino, Ed.D. (86-1100-86), 1986 (Box 178, Folder 2218)
    - Family Service Association of Nassau County - Finance - Salvatore Ambrosino, Ed.D. (86-1100-86), 1987 (Box 178, Folder 2219)
    - Family Service Association of Nassau County - Finance - Salvatore Ambrosino, Ed.D. (86-1100-86), 1987 (Box 178, Folder 2220)
    - Family Service Association of Nassau County - Reports - Salvatore Ambrosino, Ed.D. (86-1100-86), 1987 (Box 178, Folder 2220)
    - Far West Laboratory for Education - Administration - J. Ronald Lally, Ed.D. (87-0995-84), 1987-1988 (Box 178, Folder 2221)
    - Far West Laboratory for Education - Application - J. Ronald Lally, Ed.D. (87-0995-84), 1984-1985 (Box 178, Folder 2222)
    - Far West Laboratory for Education - Final Report - J. Ronald Lally, Ed.D. (87-0995-84), 1987-1988 (Box 178, Folder 2223)
    - Far West Laboratory for Education - Finance - J. Ronald Lally, Ed.D. (87-0995-84), 1987-1988 (Box 178, Folder 2224)
    - Far West Laboratory for Education - General Correspondence - J. Ronald Lally, Ed.D. (87-0995-84), 1985-1987 (Box 178, Folder 2225)
    - Far West Laboratory for Education - Reports, Publications - J. Ronald Lally, Ed.D. (87-0995-84), 1985-1987 (Box 178, Folder 2226)
    - Far West Laboratory for Education - J. Ronald Lally, Ed.D. (87-0995-84), 1984 (Box 178, Folder 2227)
    - Father Flanagan's Boys' Home - Administration - Robert McCall (85-1048-85), 1985-1986 (Box 178, Folder 2228)
    - Father Flanagan's Boys' Home - Application - Robert McCall (85-1048-85), 1985-1986 (Box 178, Folder 2229)
    - Father Flanagan's Boys' Home - Final Report - Robert McCall (85-1048-85), 1987 (Box 178, Folder 2230)
    - Father Flanagan's Boys' Home - Finance - Robert McCall (85-1048-85), 1986 (Box 178, Folder 2231)
    - Fordham University - Administration - Giuseppe Constantino, Ph.D. (83-0868-00), 1984-1987 (Box 179, Folder 2232)
    - Fordham University - Application - Giuseppe Constantino, Ph.D. (83-0868-00), 1982-1984 (Box 179, Folder 2233)
    - Fordham University - Bibliography - Giuseppe Constantino, Ph.D. (83-0868-00), after 1985 (Box 179, Folder 2234)
    - Fordham University - Finance - Giuseppe Constantino, Ph.D. (83-0868-00), 1984-1987 (Box 179, Folder 2235)
    - Fordham University - Reports, Publications - Giuseppe Constantino, Ph.D. (83-0868-00), 1985 (Box 179, Folder 2236)
    - Foundation for Advanced Education in the Sciences - Administration - Judith L. Rapoport, Ph.D. (82-0847-00), 1982-1987 (Box 179, Folder 2237)
    - Foundation for Advanced Education in the Sciences - Application - Judith L. Rapoport, Ph.D. (82-0847-00), 1982-1983 (Box 179, Folder 2238)
    - Foundation for Advanced Education in the Sciences - Final Report - Judith L. Rapoport, Ph.D. (82-0847-00), 1984-1987 (Box 179, Folder 2239)
    - Foundation for Advanced Education in the Sciences - Finance - Judith L. Rapoport, Ph.D. (82-0847-00), 1984-1987 (Box 179, Folder 2240)
    - Foundation for Advanced Education in the Sciences - Publications - Judith L. Rapoport, Ph.D. (82-0847-00), 1986 (Box 179, Folder 2241)
    - Foundation of Dramatists Guild - Administration - J. Feiffer (82-0860-00), 1982-1983 (Box 179, Folder 2242)
    - Foundation of Dramatists Guild - Application - J. Feiffer (82-0860-00), 1982 (Box 179, Folder 2243)
    - Foundation of Dramatists Guild - Finance - J. Feiffer (82-0860-00), 1982-1984 (Box 179, Folder 2244)
    - Foundation of Dramatists Guild - Reports - J. Feiffer (82-0860-00), 1984 (Box 179, Folder 2245)
    - Friendship House Children's Center - Administration - Julius Segal, Ph.D.; Zelda Segal (85-0840-82), 1982-1986 (Box 179, Folder 2246)
    - Friendship House Children's Center - Application - Julius Segal, Ph.D.; Zelda Segal (85-0840-82), 1982-1985 (Box 179, Folder 2247)
    - Friendship House Children's Center - Bibliography - Julius Segal, Ph.D.; Zelda Segal (85-0840-82), after 1987 (Box 179, Folder 2248)
    - Friendship House Children's Center - Finance - Julius Segal, Ph.D.; Zelda Segal (85-0840-82), 1983-1986 (Box 179, Folder 2249)
    - Friendship House Children's Center - Reports, Publications - Julius Segal, Ph.D.; Zelda Segal (85-0840-82), 1984-1986 (Box 179, Folder 2250)
    - Georgetown University Medical Center - Administration - Ida Sue Baron, Ph.D. (86-1112-86), 1986-1987 (Box 179, Folder 2251)
    - Georgetown University Medical Center - Application - Ida Sue Baron, Ph.D. (86-1112-86), 1985-1986 (Box 179, Folder 2252)
    - Georgetown University Medical Center - Ida Sue Baron, Ph.D. (86-1112-86), 1986 (Box 179, Folder 2253)
    - Georgetown University Medical Center - Administration - Josephine E. Pamphile (87-1189-87), 1988 (Box 179, Folder 2254)
    - Girls Club of New York - Application - Josephine E. Pamphile (87-1189-87), 1987-1988 (Box 179, Folder 2255)
    - Girls Club of New York - Finance - Josephine E. Pamphile (87-1189-87), 1988 (Box 179, Folder 2256)
    - Girls Club of New York - Program Report - Josephine E. Pamphile (87-1189-87), 1990 (Box 179, Folder 2257)
    - Girls Club of New York - Reports, Publications - Josephine E. Pamphile (87-1189-87), 1986-1990 (Box 179, Folder 2258)
    - Good Shepard Services - Administration - Sr. Paulette LoMonaco (90-0973-84), 1985-1990 (Box 179, Folder 2259)
    - Good Shepard Services - Application - Sr. Paulette LoMonaco (90-0973-84), 1984-1986 (Box 179, Folder 2260)
    - Good Shepard Services - Application - Sr. Paulette LoMonaco (90-0973-84), 1987-1988 (Box 179, Folder 2261)
    - Good Shepard Services - Finance - Sr. Paulette LoMonaco (90-0973-84), 1987-1989 (Box 180, Folder 2262)
    - Good Shepard Services - Reports - Sr. Paulette LoMonaco (90-0973-84), 1986-1989 (Box 180, Folder 2263)
    - Graham Windham - Services to Families and Children - Administration - Carmine J. Magazino; Denise Gaston (86-1070-87), 1986-1987 (Box 180, Folder 2264)
    - Graham Windham - Services to Families and Children - Application - Carmine J. Magazino; Denise Gaston (86-1070-87), 1986 (Box 180, Folder 2265)
    - Graham Windham - Services to Families and Children - Finance - Carmine J. Magazino; Denise Gaston (86-1070-87), 1986-1987 (Box 180, Folder 2266)
    - Graham Windham - Services to Families and Children - Report - Carmine J. Magazino; Denise Gaston (86-1070-87), 1987 (Box 180, Folder 2267-2268)
    - Graham Windham - Services to Families and Children - Administration - Carmine J. Magazino; Denise Gaston (87-1181-87), 1987-1988 (Box 180, Folder 2269)
    - Grant Makers in Health - Application - Catherine McDermott (87-1181-87), 1987 (Box 180, Folder 2270)
    - Grant Makers in Health - Finance - Catherine McDermott (87-1181-87), 1987-1990 (Box 180, Folder 2271)
    - Grant Makers in Health - Reports - Catherine McDermott (87-1181-87), 1989 (Box 180, Folder 2272)
    - Green Chimneys - Administration - Samuel B. Ross, Ph.D.; Aaron Katcher, M.D. (83-0908-00), 1983-1986 (Box 180, Folder 2273)
    - Green Chimneys - Application - Samuel B. Ross, Ph.D.; Aaron Katcher, M.D. (83-0908-00), 1982-1983 (Box 180, Folder 2274)
    - Green Chimneys - Application - Samuel B. Ross, Ph.D.; Aaron Katcher, M.D. (83-0908-00), 1983-1986 (Box 180, Folder 2275)
    - Harlem Dowling Children's Service - Administration - Doris H. Sims (85-1021-85), 1983-1986 (Box 180, Folder 2276)
    - Harlem Dowling Children's Service - Application - Doris H. Sims (85-1021-85), 1984-1985 (Box 180, Folder 2277)
    - Harlem Dowling Children's Service - Finance - Doris H. Sims (85-1021-85), 1984-1986 (Box 180, Folder 2278)
    - Harlem Dowling Children's Service - Report - Doris H. Sims (85-1021-85), 1985-1986 (Box 180, Folder 2279)
    - Harlem Interfaith Counseling Service - Administration - Frederick E. Dennard, M. Div. (85-1056-85), 1985-1986 (Box 180, Folder 2280)
    - Harlem Interfaith Counseling Service - Application - Frederick E. Dennard, M. Div. (85-1056-85), 1985-1986 (Box 180, Folder 2281)
    - Harlem Interfaith Counseling Service - Finance - Frederick E. Dennard, M. Div. (85-1056-85), 1986-1987 (Box 180, Folder 2282)
    - Harlem Interfaith Counseling Service - Reports - Frederick E. Dennard, M. Div. (85-1056-85), 1987 (Box 180, Folder 2283)
    - Harvard Community Health Plan - Administration - Donald Wertlieb; Donald M. Berwick (82-0835-00), 1984-1987 (Box 180, Folder 2284)
    - Harvard Community Health Plan - Application - Donald Wertlieb; Donald M. Berwick (82-0835-00), 1981-1986 (Box 180, Folder 2285-2286)
    - Harvard Community Health Plan - Final Report - Donald Wertlieb; Donald M. Berwick (82-0835-00), 1986 (Box 180, Folder 2287)
    - Harvard Community Health Plan - Final Report, Publications - Donald D. Wertlieb; Donald M. Berwick (82-0835-00), 1986 (Box 181, Folder 2288-2289)
    - Harvard Community Health Plan - Finance - Donald D. Wertlieb; Donald M. Berwick (82-0835-00), 1984-1987 (Box 181, Folder 2290)
    - Harvard Community Health Plan - Report - Donald D. Wertlieb; Donald M. Berwick (82-0835-00), 1983-1989 (Box 181, Folder 2291)
    - Harvard Community Health Plan - Report - Donald D. Wertlieb; Donald M. Berwick (82-0835-00), 1985 (Box 181, Folder 2292)
    - Harvard Community Health Plan - Donald D. Wertlieb; Donald M. Berwick (82-0835-00), 1982 (Box 181, Folder 2293)
    - Harvard University - Administration - Judith D. Singer, Ph.D. (86-1064-86), 1986 (Box 181, Folder 2294)
    - Harvard University - Application - Judith D. Singer, Ph.D. (86-1064-86), 1986-1990 (Box 181, Folder 2295)
    - Harvard University - Finance - Judith D. Singer, Ph.D. (86-1064-86), 1986-1988 (Box 181, Folder 2296)
    - Harvard University - Reports, Publications - Judith D. Singer, Ph.D. (86-1064-86), 1988 (Box 181, Folder 2297)
    - Harvard University - Administration - K. Patricia Cross (85-1038-85), 1985-1986 (Box 181, Folder 2298)
    - Harvard University - Application - K. Patricia Cross (85-1038-85), 1985-1986 (Box 181, Folder 2299)
    - Harvard University - Final Report - K. Patricia Cross (85-1038-85), 1986 (Box 181, Folder 2300-2301)
    - Harvard University - Finance - K. Patricia Cross (85-1038-85), 1986 (Box 182, Folder 2302)
    - Harvard University - Administration - Richard Katz, Ph.D. (85-1038-85), 1985-1988 (Box 182, Folder 2303)
    - Harvard University - Application - Richard Katz, Ph.D. (85-1038-85), 1985-1987 (Box 182, Folder 2304)
    - Harvard University - Final Report - Richard Katz, Ph.D. (85-1038-85), 1988 (Box 182, Folder 2305)
    - Harvard University - Finance - Richard Katz, Ph.D. (85-1038-85), 1986-1988 (Box 182, Folder 2306)
    - Harvard University - Administration - Barbara Gutmann Rosenkrantz, Ph.D.; Helen Hughes Evans (87-1143-87), 1987 (Box 182, Folder 2307)
    - Harvard University - Application - Barbara Gutmann Rosenkrantz, Ph.D.; Helen Hughes Evans (87-1143-87), 1987 (Box 182, Folder 2308)
    - Harvard University - Finance - Barbara Gutmann Rosenkrantz, Ph.D.; Helen Hughes Evans (87-1143-87), 1987-1988 (Box 182, Folder 2309)
    - Harvard University - Reports - Barbara Gutmann Rosenkrantz, Ph.D.; Helen Hughes Evans (87-1143-87), 1989 (Box 182, Folder 2310)
    - Harvard University - Administration - Dante Cicchetti, Ph.D. (83-0894-00), 1983-1986 (Box 182, Folder 2311)
    - Harvard University - Application - Dante Cicchetti, Ph.D. (83-0894-00), 1983-1984 (Box 182, Folder 2312)
    - Harvard University - Finance - Dante Cicchetti, Ph.D. (83-0894-00), 1985-1986 (Box 182, Folder 2313)
    - Harvard University - Reports - Dante Cicchetti, Ph.D. (83-0894-00), 1984-1989 (Box 182, Folder 2314)
    - Harvard University - Reports - Dante Cicchetti, Ph.D. (83-0894-00), 1986 (Box 182, Folder 2315)
    - Harvard University, Harvard Medical School - Administration - Richard N. Wolman, Ph.D. (83-0891-00), 1983-1989 (Box 182, Drawer 2316)
    - Harvard University, Harvard Medical School - Application - Richard N. Wolman, Ph.D. (83-0891-00), 1983-1984 (Box 182, Drawer 2317)
    - Harvard University, Harvard Medical School - Finance - Richard N. Wolman, Ph.D. (83-0891-00), 1983-1985 (Box 182, Drawer 2318)
    - Harvard University, Peabody Museum - Administration - Irven Devore (82-0859-00), 1984-1989 (Box 182, Drawer 2320)
    - Harvard University, Peabody Museum - Application - Irven Devore (82-0859-00), 1982-1985 (Box 183, Drawer 2321)
    - Harvard University, Peabody Museum - Finance - Irven Devore (82-0859-00), 1983-1985 (Box 183, Drawer 2322)
    - Harvard University, Peabody Museum - Reports - Irven Devore (82-0859-00), 1983-1986 (Box 183, Drawer 2323)
    - Harvard University, Peabody Museum - Irven Devore (82-0859-00), 1983 (Box 183, Drawer 2324)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Administration - William Curran, J.D. (83-0938-00), 1984-1985 (Box 183, Drawer 2325)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Application - William Curran, J.D. (83-0938-00), 1983-1984 (Box 183, Drawer 2326)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Finance - William Curran, J.D. (83-0938-00), 1985 (Box 183, Drawer 2327)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Report - William Curran, J.D. (83-0938-00), 1985 (Box 183, Drawer 2328)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Administration - Steven Gortmaker, Ph.D. (85-1031-85), 1985-1986 (Box 183, Drawer 2329)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Application - Steven Gortmaker, Ph.D. (85-1031-85), 1986-1990 (Box 183, Drawer 2330)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Final Report - Steven Gortmaker, Ph.D. (85-1031-85), 1988 (Box 183, Drawer 2331)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Finance - Steven Gortmaker, Ph.D. (85-1031-85), 1985-1988 (Box 183, Drawer 2332)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Reports, Publications - Steven Gortmaker, Ph.D. (85-1031-85), 1990 (Box 183, Drawer 2333)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Administration - Ellen C. Perrin, M.D. (83-0773-81), 1978-1988 (Box 183, Folder 2334)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Application - Ellen C. Perrin, M.D. (83-0753-81), 1981-1987 (Box 183, Folder 2335)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Finance - Ellen C. Perrin, M.D. (83-0753-81), 1981-1989 (Box 183, Folder 2336)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Report - Ellen C. Perrin, M.D. (83-0753-81), 1989-1990 (Box 183, Folder 2337)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Administration - John Eckenrode, Ph.D. (82-0810-00), 1981-1984 (Box 183, Folder 2338)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Application - John Eckenrode, Ph.D. (82-0810-00), 1981-1983 (Box 183, Folder 2339)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Finance - John Eckenrode, Ph.D. (82-0810-00), 1981-1983 (Box 183, Folder 2339b)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - Reports, Publications - John Eckenrode, Ph.D. (82-0810-00), 1982-1988 (Box 183, Folder 2340)
    - Harvard University, School of Public Health - John Eckenrode, Ph.D. (82-0810-00), 1981-1982 (Box 183, Folder 2341)
    - Health Futures Institute, Children's Health Futures - Administration - Steven R. Mosow (84-0999-84), 1984-1986 (Box 183, Folder 2342)
    - Health Futures Institute, Children's Health Futures - Application - Steven R. Mosow (84-0999-84), 1984-1985 (Box 183, Folder 2343)
    - Health Futures Institute, Children's Health Futures - Finance - Steven R. Mosow (84-0999-84), 1985 (Box 183, Folder 2344)
    - Health Futures Institute, Children's Health Futures - Final Report - Steven R. Mosow (84-0999-84), 1986 (Box 183, Folder 2345)
    - Health Futures Institute, Children's Health Futures - Report - Steven R. Mosow (84-0999-84), 1986 (Box 184, Folder 2346-2347)
    - Health Research, Inc. - Administration - Michael A. Zevon (84-046-84), 1984-1986 (Box 184, Folder 2348)
    - Health Research, Inc. - Application - Michael A. Zevon (84-046-84), 1984 (Box 184, Folder 2349)
    - Health Research, Inc. - Final Report - Michael A. Zevon (84-046-84), 1986 (Box 184, Folder 2350)
    - Health Research, Inc. - Finance - Michael A. Zevon (84-046-84), 1986 (Box 184, Folder 2351)
    - Henry Street Settlement - Administration - Dr. Michael Phillips (82-0832-00), 1982-1985 (Box 184, Folder 2351b)
    - Henry Street Settlement - Application - Dr. Michael Phillips (82-0832-00), 1981-1985 (Box 184, Folder 2352)
    - Henry Street Settlement - Finance - Dr. Michael Phillips (82-0832-00), 1983-1985 (Box 184, Folder 2353)
    - Henry Street Settlement - Reports - Dr. Michael Phillips (82-0832-00), 1984-1989 (Box 184, Folder 2354)
    - Henry Street Settlement - Administration - Daniel Kronenfeld (88-1193-88), 1987-1988 (Box 184, Folder 2355)
    - Henry Street Settlement - Application - Daniel Kronenfeld (88-1193-88), 1987-1988 (Box 184, Folder 2356)
    - Henry Street Settlement - Final Report - Daniel Kronenfeld (88-1193-88), 1984 (Box 184, Folder 2357-2358)
    - Henry Street Settlement - Finance - Daniel Kronenfeld (88-1193-88), 1989 (Box 184, Folder 2359)
    - Henry Street Settlement - Report - Daniel Kronenfeld (88-1193-88), 1989 (Box 184, Folder 2360)
    - Hospitality House - Administration - Yvonne Tibbs (82-0824-00), 1982 (Box 184, Folder 2361)
    - Hospitality House - Application - Yvonne Tibbs (82-0824-00), 1982 (Box 184, Folder 2362)
    - Hospitality House - Final Report - Yvonne Tibbs (82-0824-00), 1982-1983 (Box 184, Folder 2363)
    - Hospitality House - Finance - Yvonne Tibbs (82-0824-00), 1982-1983 (Box 184, Folder 2364)
    - University of Houston - Application - Frank S. Kessel (85-1055-85), 1985-1986 (Box 185, Folder 2366)
    - University of Houston - Final Report - Frank S. Kessel (85-1055-85), 1987 (Box 185, Folder 2367)
    - University of Houston - Finance - Frank S. Kessel (85-1055-85), 1987 (Box 185, Folder 2368)
    - Howard University - Administration - Renee R. Jenkins, M.D. (85-1029-85), 1985-1987 (Box 185, Folder 2369)
    - Howard University - Application - Renee R. Jenkins, M.D. (85-1029-85), 1985-1986 (Box 185, Folder 2370)
    - Howard University - Finance - Renee R. Jenkins, M.D. (85-1029-85), 1985-1986 (Box 185, Folder 2371)
    - Howard University - Report - Renee R. Jenkins, M.D. (85-1029-85), 1987 (Box 185, Folder 2372)
    - Hudson Guild - Administration - Arthur Zanko; Mark Farron (84-0972-84), 1984-1987 (Box 185, Folder 2373)
    - Hudson Guild - Application - Arthur Zanko; Mark Farron (84-0972-84), 1984-1986 (Box 185, Folder 2374)
    - Hudson Guild - Final Report - Arthur Zanko; Mark Farron (84-0972-84), 1985 (Box 185, Folder 2375)
    - Hudson Guild - Finance - Arthur Zanko; Mark Farron (84-0972-84), 1984-1987 (Box 185, Folder 2376)
    - Hudson Guild - Administration - Janice McGuire (87-1168-87)), 1987-1989 (Box 185, Folder 2377)
    - Hudson Guild - Application - Janice McGuire (87-1168-87)), 1987-1989 (Box 185, Folder 2378)
    - Hudson Guild - Finance - Janice McGuire (87-1168-87)), 1987-1989 (Box 185, Folder 2379)
    - Hudson Guild - Reports - Janice McGuire (87-1168-87)), 1988 (Box 185, Folder 2380)
    - Human Resources Center of St. Albans - Administration - George C. Allen (85-1019-85) (Box 185, Folder 2381)
    - Human Resources Center of St. Albans - Application - George C. Allen (85-1019-85), 1984-1986 (Box 185, Folder 2382)
    - Human Resources Center of St. Albans - Finance - George C. Allen (85-1019-85), 1985-1986 (Box 185, Folder 2383)
    - Human Resources Center of St. Albans - Report - George C. Allen (85-1019-85), 1986 (Box 185, Folder 2384)
    - University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaigne - Administration - Kennedy T. Hill (86-1085-86), 1986-1987 (Box 185, Folder 2385)
    - University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaigne - Application - Kennedy T. Hill (86-1085-86), 1986-1987 (Box 185, Folder 2386)
    - University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaigne - Final Report - Kennedy T. Hill (86-1085-86), 1987 (Box 185, Folder 2387)
    - University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaigne - Finance - Kennedy T. Hill (86-1085-86), 1988 (Box 185, Folder 2388)
    - University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaigne - Kennedy T. Hill (86-1085-86), 1986 (Box 185, Folder 2389)
    - University of Illinois, Urbana-Champaigne - Administration - Rita J. Simon, Ph.D. (83-0895-00), 1983-1985 (Box 185, Folder 2390)